{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":990,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":1024,"height":627,"responsive":false,"scalable":true,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"SmartShape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_1","title":"Start! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4353","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4366","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Start! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Image_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Image_1","roles":{}},{"id":"Slide4269","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_1","si4353","si4366","Image_1"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4269"}}},{"id":"si6034","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_21","title":"What was the name of the town where was Jesus born? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6045","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_27","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6049","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_28","title":"Bethlehem ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6045_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Bethelehem\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si6056","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_29","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6060","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_30","title":"Cana ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6056_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cana\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_31","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6071","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_32","title":"Samaria ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6067_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Samaria\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6195","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_11","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6232q0","for":"Slide6232q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6207","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6232q0","for":"Slide6232q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6219","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6232q0","for":"Slide6232q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_12","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6232q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_13","title":"Almost! Jesus was born in Bethlehem. Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6232q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6159","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_14","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6232q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6232","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6034","si6049","si6060","si6071","si6195","si6207","si6219","si6159"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6232"},"question":{"interactionId":"6020","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What was the name of the town where was Jesus born?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6268","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_22","title":"Jesus was wrapped in swaddling clothes and was placed in a ___________? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6279","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_33","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6283","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_34","title":" crib ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6279_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_18","roles":{"answer":{"title":" crib\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6290","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_35","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6294","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_36","title":"manger ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6290_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_19","roles":{"answer":{"title":"manger\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si6301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_37","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6305","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_38","title":"stroller ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6301_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_20","roles":{"answer":{"title":"stroller\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6429","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_12","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6466q1","for":"Slide6466q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6441","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6466q1","for":"Slide6466q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6453","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6466q1","for":"Slide6466q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6343","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_15","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6466q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6362","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"Almost! Jesus was placed a manger. Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6466q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_17","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6466q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6466","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6268","si6283","si6294","si6305","si6429","si6441","si6453","si6393"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6466"},"question":{"interactionId":"6254","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Jesus was wrapped in swaddling clothes and was placed in a ___________?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6502","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_23","title":"Joseph and Mary tried to find an inn to stay in when they got to Bethlehem, but they were all full.  Where did they end up staying? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_39","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6517","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_40","title":"a house ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6513_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_21","roles":{"answer":{"title":"a house\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6524","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_41","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6528","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_42","title":"a stable ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6524_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_22","roles":{"answer":{"title":"a stable\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si6535","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_43","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6539","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_44","title":"a tent ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6535_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_23","roles":{"answer":{"title":"a tent\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6663","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_13","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6700q2","for":"Slide6700q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6675","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6700q2","for":"Slide6700q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6687","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6700q2","for":"Slide6700q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6577","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6700q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6596","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"Almost! They ended up staying in a stable.  Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6700q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6627","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_20","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6700q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6700","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6502","si6517","si6528","si6539","si6663","si6675","si6687","si6627"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6700"},"question":{"interactionId":"6488","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Joseph and Mary tried to find an inn to stay in when they got to Bethlehem, but they were all full. \rWhere did they end up staying?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6736","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_24","title":"Who did an angel of the Lord appear to after Jesus was born? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6747","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_45","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6751","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_46","title":"Herod, the king of Judea  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6747_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_24","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Herod, the king of Judea \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6758","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_47","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6762","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_48","title":"shepherds keeping watch over their flocks  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6758_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_25","roles":{"answer":{"title":"shepherds keeping watch over their flocks \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si6769","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_49","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6773","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_50","title":"the innkeeper and his wife ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6769_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_26","roles":{"answer":{"title":"the innkeeper and his wife\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6897","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_14","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6934q3","for":"Slide6934q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6909","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6934q3","for":"Slide6934q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6921","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide6934q3","for":"Slide6934q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6811","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6934q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6830","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_22","title":"Almost! The angel of the Lord appeared to shepherds who were keeping watch over their flocks by night.  Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6934q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6861","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_23","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide6934q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6934","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6736","si6751","si6762","si6773","si6897","si6909","si6921","si6861"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6934"},"question":{"interactionId":"6722","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Who did an angel of the Lord appear to after Jesus was born?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si6970","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_25","title":"What gifts did the three wise men bring to baby Jesus, the newborn king? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6981","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_51","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6985","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_52","title":"fruits, vegetables and bread ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6981_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_27","roles":{"answer":{"title":"fruits, vegetables and bread\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si6992","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_53","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6996","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_54","title":"gold, frankincense and myrrh ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6992_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_28","roles":{"answer":{"title":"gold, frankincense and myrrh\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si7003","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_55","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7007","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_56","title":"books, clothes and shoes ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7003_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_29","roles":{"answer":{"title":"books, clothes and shoes\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_15","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7168q4","for":"Slide7168q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7143","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7168q4","for":"Slide7168q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7155","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7168q4","for":"Slide7168q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7045","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7168q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7064","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_25","title":"Almost! The three wise men brought baby Jesus gold, frankincense and myrrh.  Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7168q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7095","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7168q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7168","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6970","si6985","si6996","si7007","si7131","si7143","si7155","si7095"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7168"},"question":{"interactionId":"6956","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What gifts did the three wise men bring to baby Jesus, the newborn king?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si7438","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_63","title":"How did the wise men know where to find baby Jesus? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7449","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_64","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7453","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_65","title":"They were given directions.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7449_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_33","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They were given directions. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7460","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_66","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7464","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_67","title":"They followed a very, bright new star in the sky.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7460_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_34","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They followed a very, bright new star in the sky. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si7471","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_68","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7475","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_69","title":"They guess where they might find baby Jesus.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7471_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_35","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They guess where they might find baby Jesus. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7599","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_17","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7636q5","for":"Slide7636q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7611","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7636q5","for":"Slide7636q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7623","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7636q5","for":"Slide7636q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7513","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7636q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7532","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"Almost! The three wise men brought baby Jesus gold, frankincense and myrrh.  Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7636q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7563","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7636q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7636","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si7438","si7453","si7464","si7475","si7599","si7611","si7623","si7563"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7636"},"question":{"interactionId":"7424","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"How did the wise men know where to find baby Jesus?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si7672","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_70","title":"Why did the three wise men want to find baby Jesus and bring him gifts?  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7683","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_71","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7687","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_72","title":"They wanted to see where the bright star would lead. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7683_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_36","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They wanted to see where the bright star would lead.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7694","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_73","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7698","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_74","title":"They wanted to worship and meet the Messiah or Savior of all mankind.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7694_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_37","roles":{"answer":{"title":"They wanted to worship and meet the Messiah or Savior of all mankind. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si7705","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_75","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7709","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_76","title":"Because they were friends with Mary and Joseph.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7705_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_38","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Because they were friends with Mary and Joseph. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7833","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_18","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7870q6","for":"Slide7870q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7845","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7870q6","for":"Slide7870q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7857","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7870q6","for":"Slide7870q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7747","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7870q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7766","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_34","title":"Almost! The three wise men brought baby Jesus gifts because they wanted to worship and meet the Messiah or Savior of all mankind. Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7870q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7797","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide7870q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7870","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si7672","si7687","si7698","si7709","si7833","si7845","si7857","si7797"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7870"},"question":{"interactionId":"7658","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"Why did the three wise men want to find baby Jesus and bring him gifts? \r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si7906","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_77","title":"What is the true meaning and reason we celebrate Christmas? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7917","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_78","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7921","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_79","title":"To celebrate and give thanks for the greatest and most precious gift of all: Jesus Christ, the Savior that was born. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7917_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"13_39","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To celebrate and give thanks for the greatest and most precious gift of all: Jesus Christ, the Savior that was born.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":1}}}},{"id":"si7928","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_80","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7932","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_81","title":"To celebrate the winter, the snow and the cold weather.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7928_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"15_40","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To celebrate the winter, the snow and the cold weather. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7939","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_82","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7943","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_83","title":"To ask Santa Claus for presents and things that we want.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7939_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"17_41","roles":{"answer":{"title":"To ask Santa Claus for presents and things that we want. \r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si8067","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_19","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8104q7","for":"Slide8104q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8104q7","for":"Slide8104q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8091","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check my answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide8104q7","for":"Slide8104q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7981","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"You got it! Click anywhere to continue! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8104q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8000","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_37","title":"Almost! The three wise men brought baby Jesus gifts because they wanted to worship and meet the Messiah or Savior of all mankind. Click anywhere to continue. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8104q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8031","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_38","title":"Please take a guess before continuing!  ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide8104q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8104","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si7906","si7921","si7932","si7943","si8067","si8079","si8091","si8031"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8104"},"question":{"interactionId":"7892","quizId":387,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"What is the true meaning and reason we celebrate Christmas?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["1"],"score":{"weight":1,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si4645","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Nativity & Christmas Quiz ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4641","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You Scored: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4689","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si4693","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4710","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si4723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide4621","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide4621"}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_2","title":"Want to learn more about the Christmas story and the Nativity?  Check out your Bible specifically in the Gospels of Matthew and Luke Chapters 1 and 2! ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_3","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_3","title":"Exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8195","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si8216","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Exit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8115","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_2","SmartShape_3","si8195","si8216"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8115"}}},{"id":"Pool431","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":431,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"CNquiz","class":"project","title":"CNquiz","children":["Slide4269","Slide6232","Slide6466","Slide6700","Slide6934","Slide7168","Slide7636","Slide7870","Slide8104","Slide4621","Slide8115"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":387,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":false,"questions":["Slide6232q0","Slide6466q1","Slide6700q2","Slide6934q3","Slide7168q4","Slide7636q5","Slide7870q6","Slide8104q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":8,"passScore":7}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide4269","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide6232","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide6466","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide6700","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide6934","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide7168","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide7636","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide7870","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8104","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide4621","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide8115","title":"Slide 11"}]}